(Penny:)Uh, well, you know
your private bathroom?
(Dan:)Yeah?
That was supposed to
be for the whole floor.
(Bernadette:)You're kidding.
DAN:
No, no.
(Dan:)It's okay. It only really
affected Wheelchair Kathy,
(Dan:)and she's back
in the hospital now,
(Dan:)so it all worked out.
(Bernadette:)I feel so bad.
Yeah.
(Penny:)Well, then, maybe
(Penny:)you shouldn't have named her
"Wheelchair Kathy."
Oh, my God!
(Bernadette:)I thought everybody liked me,
but I'm just a monster.
(Dan:)But a cute one, like that, uh,
eyeball guy in Monsters, Inc.
(Bernadette:)No, I'm the worst.
(Bernadette:)I'm a terrible person.
(Dan:)Come on, don't cry.
It's okay.
(crying):
It's not okay.
(Bernadette:)How can I even work here
anymore?
Oh.
(Penny:)Because this company needs you.
DAN:
It's fine.
(Dan:)We don't mind paying
for the coffee.
(Bernadette:)I can't let you do that.
(Dan:)Maybe we could get you
(Dan:)an espresso machine
for your office.
(crying):
I guess that would be all right.
(Penny:)All right.
(crying)
See? You don't have
(Penny:)to be mean
to get what you want.